<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Physical Constants - articles</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/articles.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2024-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><subtitle>Where the ethereal meets the ever-changing</subtitle><entry><title>Ch-Ch-Ch Changes</title><link href="/ch-ch-ch-changes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Bo Johnson</name></author><id>tag:None,2024-03-02:/ch-ch-ch-changes.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I want to talk about why I made the change from using Julia to Python&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="articles"></category><category term="python"></category><category term="julia"></category></entry><entry><title>Introduction to Physical Constants</title><link href="/introduction-to-physical-constants.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-28T10:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-02-28T10:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Bo Johnson</name></author><id>tag:None,2024-02-28:/introduction-to-physical-constants.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Why this blog?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I find my thinking gets sharpened and my mind clearer
when I write down all that's in my head. It's easy for stuff
to get lost up there and my experience with graduate school
has been to work on many different things at once. So much …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Why this blog?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I find my thinking gets sharpened and my mind clearer
when I write down all that's in my head. It's easy for stuff
to get lost up there and my experience with graduate school
has been to work on many different things at once. So much
so that I often forget what I have worked on only a year prior.
(I do have things in my logbook or I can look back at code, but
the fast pace of switching between so many projects for me has
been a whirlwind.) So hopefully taking the time to put things
I'm working on down in a longer, more carefully thought-out
format will cement them in my head, rather than flying about
with every change of the wind. Additionally, by writing more
frequently I'm hoping to develop better as a writer for the
future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What will I write about?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm mainly going to write about my research and related topics.
This will include what little theory I know (I'm no theorist or 
phenomenologist) so those posts will invariably contain mistakes
that are my own. But I'll also write about analysis and coding
and even personal adventures as I go along. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;How often will I write?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's the great question. I'm hoping I can write a post a week,
that should motivate me to learn something interesting to write
about or showcase what I've been working on. In any case, this
is more a moonshot than a guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Who is this blog for?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm guessing only my mom would take the time to read this. Hi,
Mom!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Articles"></category><category term="intro"></category></entry></feed>